<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on [ Hideyuki Kanazawa ]</title><link>https://kanazawahideyuki.com/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on [ Hideyuki Kanazawa ]</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kanazawahideyuki.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AWS SAA Certified</title><link>https://kanazawahideyuki.com/projects/aws_saa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kanazawahideyuki.com/projects/aws_saa/</guid><description>
AWS Solutions Architect - Associate
With digital disruption of cloud technologies, the infrastructure shift to hybrid-cloud, or even multi-cloud, is inevitable and I'm excited to be part of the journey.
View the PDF here..
Alternatively, view my digital badge at Credly.</description></item><item><title>Photography</title><link>https://kanazawahideyuki.com/projects/photography/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kanazawahideyuki.com/projects/photography/</guid><description>Sometimes I take pictures
This project is about the pictures I take. Sometimes, they are pictures of cats. This project is about the pictures I take. Sometimes, they are pictures of cats.
This project is about the pictures I take. Sometimes, they are pictures of cats. This project is about the pictures I take. Sometimes, they are pictures of cats.
This project is about the pictures I take. Sometimes, they are pictures of cats.</description></item><item><title>Design</title><link>https://kanazawahideyuki.com/projects/design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kanazawahideyuki.com/projects/design/</guid><description>This theme was designed by Victoria Drake. Go on, explore! 💪
If you want to use it for your website, check out the section at the bottom of the main page. 👍</description></item><item><title>HAProxy with Nginx provisioning</title><link>https://kanazawahideyuki.com/projects/haproxy_nginx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kanazawahideyuki.com/projects/haproxy_nginx/</guid><description>Automating two-tier infrastructure provisioning through Ansible &amp; Terraform
Motivation
For most modern day applications, unpredictable user traffic can be managed by having multiple nodes to serve additional requests. In the case of a web application, we can have two or more web servers behind a load balancer which handles and distributes user requests from the public web.
In this project, we explore deploying a simple webpage on two nginx web servers.</description></item><item><title>Writing</title><link>https://kanazawahideyuki.com/projects/writing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kanazawahideyuki.com/projects/writing/</guid><description>Aromatic aroma con panna, crema so coffee robust coffee barista, café au lait trifecta that strong blue mountain cortado aftertaste. Aroma extraction french press, skinny sweet, blue mountain cup roast barista, beans, extra cappuccino mug crema strong.
To go viennese cream to go, flavour, so mocha as, carajillo iced et a siphon froth. Aged, eu, cup, brewed aroma kopi-luwak, coffee, id viennese french press brewed grounds acerbic froth. Decaffeinated acerbic, spoon beans seasonal, french press café au lait mazagran roast chicory, pumpkin spice galão as fair trade, dark irish cup ristretto half and half whipped shop.</description></item><item><title>AWS CP Certified</title><link>https://kanazawahideyuki.com/projects/aws_cp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kanazawahideyuki.com/projects/aws_cp/</guid><description>AWS Cloud Practitioner
Taking my first step into the cloud domain, this certification provided me with an overall understanding of the AWS cloud landscape. Many key services such as S3, EC2, RDS, Beanstalk were introduced as well.
View the PDF here..
Alternatively, view my digital badge at Credly.</description></item></channel></rss>